[
    {
        "question":"What did people use as money in ancient Mesopotamia? Where did they store it?",
        "answer":"People used grain as money and stored it in safe places such as temples and palaces."
    },
    
    {
        "question":"Where did the first bank open in the US?",
        "answer":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania"
    } ,
    
    
    {
        "question":"What is the full form of an ATM?",
        "answer":"Automatic Teller Machine"
    },
    
    {
        "question":"Who is a teller?",
        "answer":"Tellers are people who help the customers. "
    },
    
    {
        "question":"How does the teller help the boy?",
        "answer":"She shows his savings account by entering his account number into the computer. An account number is long and no two account numbers are alike."
    },
    
    {
        "question":"What activity does the boy see on his bank account?",
        "answer":"He notices deposits (putting money in the bank) and withdrawal (taking money out of the bank) and a deposit he didnâ€™t remember making called an interest."
    },
    
    
    {
        "question":"What is an interest?",
        "answer":"An interest is what the bank pays people to keep their money (deposit) in the bank. When people borrow money (loan), they pay an interest to the bank."
    },
    
    
    {
        "question":"What are the two main jobs of a bank?",
        "answer":"To be a safe place to keep our money, and to lend money to people for big purchases like a home."
    }  ,
    
    
    {
        "question":"What is a check?",
        "answer":"A check is like a letter to the bank from another bank. It tells the bank to give money to whomever is named on the check."
    },
    
    {
        "question":"What is a federal reserve bank?",
        "answer":"It is a central bank where all the old bills go to be transformed into new bills. There are 12 FRBs in the US for each region. They are like banks for banks."
    },
    
    
    {
        "question":"Why does the bank have a vault?",
        "answer":"To keep money and safe-deposit boxes in a secure and fireproof room. People rent safe-deposit boxes to keep items such as jewellery and legal papers."
    }
]